# Jorge León Salas

### XR Designer and Developer

jorge.leons@outlook.com

Q Canada / Vancouver BC

<u>LinkedIn</u>

% Portfolio

# PROFILE

I'm a Mexican computer scientist with a diploma on XR design and development.

I love being part of the entire process when it comes to create stuff to design solutions that take in consideration every possible point of view. I enjoy trying and developing experiences in game engines in my free time and would like to focus on user experience, such as intuitiveness and accessibility.

# SKILLS

#### 9 / 10

Unity and C#

#### 8 / 10

Unreal Engine and Blueprints

#### 9/10

Teamwork and adaptability

#### 8 / 10

Leadership and assertiveness

#### 7 / 10

HTML, CSS, React, Javascript

# EDUCATION

VR/AR Design and Development Vancouver Film School - 2022

Computer Science Engineering Instituto Tecnologico y de Estudios Superiores de Monterrey - 2016 – 2020

Videogame design / programming introductory course

Vancouver Film School - 2019

# EXPERIENCE

### Graduate QA Automation Engineer

Solera, Inc / Mexico City, Santa Fe / December 2020 – December 2021

I worked with an internal framework that was mostly based on Selenium and C#. Alongside my manager, we created the first project to use the latest framework, combined with a structure for test cases and great OOP practices, we provided a base project which eliminated the necessity to run the automation project manually and locally, decreased the run time from 3 hours to 30 minutes, added the possibility to schedule runs, and have everything automatically reported to TestRail.

### Digital Innovation & Technology – IT Applications Intern

Schneider Electric / Mexico City, Polanco / September 2019 – June 2020

I mostly developed and maintained web applications. I took part on the development from scratch of a process that eliminated the manual necessity for the annual verification of registered clients.

# PROJECTS

Cyber Attack / Vancouver Film School, Vancouver BC / 2022

A VR based board and FPS game, where I took the role of game programmer for many interactions. It was developed as the final project on the VR/AR design and development course on Unreal Engine 5 with blueprints.

TTT Studios, Dementia / Vancouver Film School, Vancouver BC / 2022

A story-based experience, developed in Unity, where the user will see visual impairments that try to imitate dementia symptoms. It was delivered as the client project for TTT Studios on the VR/AR design and development program at Vancouver Film School.